A Finding Aid to the Institute of Contemporary Arts Records, 1927-circa 1985, bulk 1947-1967, in the Archives of American Art AAA.instcona
Archives of American Art
- ICA Program Files, circa 1947-1968; Series 3; 5.2 Linear feet Boxes 8-13, 27
  - Congress of Artists and Writers (5th: 1963), 1959-1963 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Crafts Project Proposal, circa 1947-1950s (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Cravo, Mario, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Cravo, Mario (Fall 1964) (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Cravo, Mario, Traveling Exhibition, 1965-1967 (Box 9, Folder 38-42)
  - Cravo, Mario, Traveling Exhibition, 1964-1967 (Box 10, Folder 1-9)
  - "The Dance in Contemporary American Indian Art" Exhibition, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Dancers of Uganda, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - "Dutch Art, 1945-1955" (Jan. 4 - Feb. 2, 1958), 1957-1958 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Dutilleux, Henri (Mar. 4, 1965), 1964-1965 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - T.S. Eliot Memorial Service (Feb. 1965), 1964-1965 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Engraver's Workshop, circa 1950-1951 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Eto, Kimio (Oct. 1963) (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Exhibitions (1952) (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Exhibitions and Programs (1953) (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Exhibitions, 1956-1960 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Exhibitions, Miscellaneous Empty Folders, circa 1950s-1960s (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - [Film Series?], 1961 January (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - "From Latin America" Exhibition (Dec. 16, 1956 - Feb. 17, 1957), 1956-1957 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - "From Peru" Exhibition (Jan. 20 - Mar. 4, 1956), 1955-1956 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Georgetown University 175th Anniversary, 1963-1964 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - "German Painting Today" Exhibition (1956), 1955-1956 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Ginestera, Alberto, 1965-1966 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Ginestera, Alberto and Manuel Mujica Lainez (1967), 1965-1967 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - "Handmade in India Today", 1955-1956 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Harkness Ballet (Feb. 1, 1967) (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Hepworth, Barbara, Exhibition, circa 1954-1956 (Box 10, Folder 30-31)
  - Paul Hindemith Opera and Ballet Production (Mar. 17-18, 1963), 1962-1963 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Homage to E.M. Forster, 1959 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - ICA Artists Tape Recordings, circa 1947-1967 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - "Image of Chile" (Oct. 13, 1963) (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Index Cards, 1950s-1960s (Box 10, Folder 36)
    Index cards housed in shoebox in Box 27
  - International Cultural Exchange Program, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - José Limón Dance Company (Feb. 9, 1966), 1965-1966 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - José Limón Dance Company, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - José Limón Dance Company (Feb. 21-24, 1968) (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Finn Juhl Exhibition (Dec. 3, 1955 - Jan. 8, 1956), 1947-1960 (Box 10, Folder 41-42)
  - Julliard School of Music, "Elegy for Young Lovers", 1965-1966 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Korean Dancers, 1963-1964 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Kyogen Drama (Feb. 1-2, 1964), 1963-1964 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - "Latin American Painting - USA 1963" Exhibition, 1963-1964 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Leach, Bernard, Pottery Exhibition, 1949-1955 (Box 11, Folder 5-21)
  - Leach, Bernard, "A Potter's Portfolio", 1949-1953 (Box 11, Folder 22-24)
  - Leach, Bernard, U.S. Visit (Mar. 15 - May 15, 1960), 1959-1960 (Box 11, Folder 25-26)
  - Lisner Auditorium Dance Performances Ticket Requests [Limón, Graham and others], 1949-1950 (Box 12, Folder 1-2)
  - Lisner Auditorium Series, 1948-1951 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Litvin, Natasha, Concert, 1953-1957 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Magazine Proposal, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Martha Graham Dance Company, 1949-1950 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Martha Graham Dance Company (Oct. 10-11, 1966), 1966-1967 (Box 12, Folder 7-8)
  - Miscellaneous, 1948-1960s (Box 12, Folder 9-11)
  - Moore, Henry (General), 1965 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Moore, Henry, Traveling Exhibition, 1959; 1964-1966 (Box 12, Folder 13-21)
  - Morris, George L.K., Exhibition, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Muir, Edwin, 1955-1959 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Munakata/Hamada Exhibition, 1952-1953 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Nabokov, Nicholas, 1964-1965 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Noguchi, Isumi, Exhibition (Fall 1955), 1955-1956 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Okada, Kenzo, 1955-1956 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Old Lyme Exhibition, 1966-1967 (Box 12, Folder 28-30)
  - Paul Taylor Dance Company (1967), 1965-1967 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - "The Play of Daniel" and "The Play of Herod", 1964-1967 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - "The Play of Daniel" (Dec. 1964) and "The Play of Herod" (Jan. 1965), 1964-1965 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - "The Play of Daniel" (Dec. 1966) and "The Play of Herod" (Jan. 1967), 1966-1967 (Box 12, Folder 34-35)
  - Poetry and Play Readings (1951-1952), 1950-1952 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - "Pottery, Calligraphy and Shaker Arts" Exhibition (Feb. 9 - Mar. 13, 1966), 1965-1966 (Box 12, Folder 37-38)
  - "Pottery From Vallauris" Exhibition, 1950-1958 (Box 12, Folder 39-42)
  - Rao, Shanta, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Richter, Hans, 1947-1960 (Box 13, Folder 2-3)
  - Seferis, George, 1963-1965 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - "Six Japanese Painters," Paintings from Japan Today (June 10 - Sept. 1, 1957) (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Spanish Painting Exhibition (Aug. 11 - Sept. 12, 1964) (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Subbulakshmi, M.S. (Oct. 21, 1966), 1965-1966 (Box 13, Folder 7-8)
  - Tomlin, Bradley, Exhibition, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Translation Program, 1959-1961 (Box 13, Folder 10-15)
  - University Consortium, 1959-1967 (Box 13, Folder 16-21)
  - Vedova, Emilio, 1965-1966 (Box 13, Folder 22-23)
  - Visiting Artists, early 1960s (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Washington Watercolor Association (Apr. 30 - May 27, 1967) (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - West African Dance (Oct. 1964), 1964-1965 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Wright, Frank Lloyd, Exhibition (1957), 1957-1959 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Wright, Frank Lloyd, Lectures (Oct. 14, 1957 and Oct. 3, 1958), 1956-1959 (Box 13, Folder 28-30)
  - "Young British Painters" Exhibition, 1957-1958 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Young Ireland Theater Company Tour, 1951-1952 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - "Younger American Painters" Exhibition, 1956-1957 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Index Cards, ICA Appearances of Foreign Artists (1958-1967), 1950s-1960s (Box 27, Folder 1)
    Index cards from Box 10, Folder 36 in shoebox
  - Index Cards, Potential Lecturers, 1950s-1960s (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Organizations, 1940s-1967; 1927; circa 1951-1967; Series 4; 7.3 Linear feet Boxes 13-20, OV 39
  4.1 General, 1955-1967
  4.2 People-to-People Program, 1927, 1940s, circa 1951, 1954-1963
  - General, 1955-1967; 4.1
    Found are files related to various governmental and non-profit organizations, predominately arts or international exchange organizations based in Washington, D.C., with which ICA or Richman collaborated. Materials include mostly printed materials such as bulletins, brochures, schedules, reports, and press releases. Also found is correspondence, notes, and scattered financial records.
    Folders are arranged alphabetically by organization name.
    - American Association of Museums, 1958-1963 (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - The American National Theater and Academy, circa 1958 (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - Arena Stage, 1961-1964 (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - "Art for the City," National Institute of Public Affairs, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Catholic University Building Fund, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - City Tavern Association, 1960-1961 (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - Colby College Sesquicentennial Project, "Art in Maine", 1962 (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - Committee on International Exchange of Persons, 1961-1962 (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - Cultural Task Force (Department of State), 1961 (Box 13, Folder 42)
    - D.C. Arts Council, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 43)
    - D.C. Recreation Board, 1963-1967 (Box 14, Folder 1-2)
    - Greater Washington Council of Organizations Serving International Visitors, 1960-1963 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Greater Washington Music Council, Miss Eversman, 1958-1960 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Inaugural Ceremonies (1960; President John F. Kennedy), 1960-1961; 1963 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Inaugural Committee (1964; President Lyndon B. Johnson), 1959; 1964-1965 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Institute of International Education, 1958-1967 (Box 14, Folder 7-11)
    - International Cultural Exchange Program, Young Artists Project (IIE), 1960 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - International Museum, Liebman, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - International Student House, 1961-1962 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - International Visitors Service (IVIS), 1962-1967 (Box 14, Folder 15-16)
    - List of Organizational Contacts, 1956-1965 (Box 14, Folder 17-18)
    - National Council on Arts and Government, 1963-1964 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - National Cultural Center [and Washington Festival Committee], 1958 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - National Cultural Center, Kennedy Center, 1961-1966 (Box 14, Folder 21-25)
    - National Endowment for the Arts; National Endowment for the Humanities, circa 1967 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - National Foundation on Arts and Humanities, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - National Gallery of Art, 1955 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - NETV Films, 1962-1964 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - The Opera Society of Washington, 1960-1966 (Box 14, Folder 30-31)
    - Patrick Hayes Concert Bureau, 1958-1960 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Robie House, 1957-1958 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - THIS (The Hospitality and Information Service), 1961-1964 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - United Performing Arts of Washington, 1965-1967 (Box 15, Folder 2-4)
    - United States. State Department, 1957-1959 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - University Center in Virginia, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Washington Arts Council, 1962-1964 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Washington Ballet Guild, Members and Trustees, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Washington Classical Club, circa 1960s (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Washington Drama Society, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Washington Film Society, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Washington Gallery of Modern Art, 1962-1963 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Washington International Center, American Council on Education, 1958-1964 (Box 15, Folder 13-14)
    - Washington International Center, Programs, 1960-1964 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - WETA-TV, 1962-1967 (Box 15, Folder 16-17)
  - People-to-People Program, 1940s; 1927; 1954-1963; circa 1951; 4.2
    The People-to-People Program was an international exchange initiative of President Dwight D. Eisenhower begun in 1956. The program had numerous committees for a variety of initiatives; Richard Richman was on the Executive Committee of Fine Arts Committee (FAC) and was elected president circa 1963. These files, which appear to be those of FAC Executive Director Eleanor Mitchell, were probably given to Richman at that time. Materials include incoming and outgoing correspondence, exhibition files, printed materials and other documents related to FAC's work organizing exhibitions and exchanges from 1956-1963. Also found are printed materials and correspondence regarding other People-to-People committees.
    - Affiliations (Cities, Universities, Etc.), 1957-1961 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Book Committee, 1957-1960 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Civic Committee, 1957-1961 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Clippings, 1956-1960 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Committee for the Handicapped, 1957-1961 (Box 15, Folder 22-23)
    - Fine Arts Committee (FAC), 1956-1963 (Box 15, Folder 24-26)
    - Fine Arts Committee (FAC) (Box 15)
      - Approach to Foundations Report, 1957 (Box 15, Folder 27)
      - Art Personnel: Japanese Art Student Association, 1960-1961 (Box 15, Folder 28)
      - Artist: Teruo Hara (Japanese), 1956-1960 (Box 15, Folder 29-30)
      - Asst. Information on FAC Activities, 1958-1961 (Box 15, Folder 31)
      - Budget (1960-1961), 1957-1961 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Fine Arts Committee (FAC) (Box 16)
      - Busts of Statesmen - General Information, 1957-1960 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - Chairmen, 1958-1961 (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - Children's Art Exchange, 1959-1961 (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - Clippings, 1957-1961 (Box 16, Folder 4-5)
      - Committee on American Art in American Embassies, 1956-1961 (Box 16, Folder 6-7)
      - Committee on Exchange of Information and Personnel, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 8)
      - Committee on Publications, 1956-1958 (Box 16, Folder 9)
      - Committee on Slides, Film Strips, 1957-1958 (Box 16, Folder 10)
      - Corcoran Gallery Staff, 1957-1961 (Box 16, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence, Outgoing, 1957-1960 (Box 16, Folder 12-25)
    - Fine Arts Committee (FAC) (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence, Outgoing, 1960-1961 (Box 17, Folder 1-6)
      - Correspondence re: FAC Funds (1957-1960) (Box 17, Folder 7-8)
      - Correspondence, Reply Pending, 1960-1961 (Box 17, Folder 9)
      - Decoration of American Embassies (General), 1959-1961 (Box 17, Folder 10)
      - Decoration of American Embassies: IBM, 1958-1960 (Box 17, Folder 11)
      - Decoration of Embassies: Rosenwald Loans, 1957-1961 (Box 17, Folder 12)
      - Decoration of Embassy Projects: George Washington Portrait Reported to be by Gilbert Stuart, Calcutta, India, 1957-1961; circa 1925 (Box 17, Folder 13)
      - Deposits: Pictures of German Works of Art and Architecture in Zentral-Institute, Munich, Germany Thru M. Kade, 1958-1960 (Box 17, Folder 14)
      - Deposits: Reproductions of George P.A. Healy's Portrait of Abraham Lincoln, 1960-1961 (Box 17, Folder 15)
      - Deposits: Sculpture Reproductions at National Museum, Bangkok, Thailand, 1957-1959 (Box 17, Folder 16)
      - Deposits: Slides and Reproductions (General), 1957-1961 (Box 17, Folder 17)
      - Deposits: Slides and Reproductions, Jogjakarta, Indonesia (Mr. Affandi), 1958-1959 (Box 17, Folder 18)
      - Deposits: Slides and Reproductions, Krakow, Poland, 1957-1961 (Box 17, Folder 19)
      - Deposits: Slides at University of Antioquia, Medellín, Colombia, 1957-1959 (Box 17, Folder 20)
      - Deposits: Slides at University of the Punjab, Lahore, Pakistan, 1957-1958 (Box 17, Folder 21)
      - Deposits: Slides, Film Strips, Publications in Soviet Union - Result of Visits by Artists Watkins, Dodd, Etc., 1958-1960 (Box 17, Folder 22-23)
      - Deposits: Slides for Seoul, Korea (Proposed), 1958 (Box 17, Folder 24)
      - Embassy and Foreign Contacts, 1958-1961 (Box 17, Folder 25)
      - Exchange: Ceramic with Academic Internationale de la Ceramique, Geneva, Switzerland, 1956-1960 (Box 17, Folder 26)
      - Exchange: Student Art with Assumption Convent in Manila, 1958-1959 (Box 17, Folder 27)
      - Exchange of Art Slides Requested by Ube City Library, Japan, 1958-1961 (Box 17, Folder 28)
      - Exchange of Exhibitions, 1956-1961 (Box 17, Folder 29)
      - Exchange of Exhibitions: P-to-P Committee of the Arts of South Africa (Contemporary Prints from L.C.), 1959-1961 (Box 17, Folder 30-31)
    - Fine Arts Committee (FAC) (Box 18)
      - Exchange of Personnel, 1957-1961 (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - Exchange of Personnel: 220 Architects from Milan, 1958-1959 (Box 18, Folder 2-3)
      - Exchange of Personnel: Bolshoi Ballet and Russian Festival, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - Exchange of Personnel: Dr. Mujica of Buenos Aires, 1960-1961; 1956 (Box 18, Folder 5)
      - Exchange of Personnel: Dr. Hans Pauer of Vienna, Austria, 1958-1960 (Box 18, Folder 6)
      - Exchange of Personnel: Proposed Visit of Art Inspector from Colombo, 1958-1959 (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - Exchange of Personnel: Seminar on American Art and Culture, 1958-1960 (Box 18, Folder 8)
      - Exchange of Personnel: Swissair Trip, 1956-1959 (Box 18, Folder 9)
      - Exchange of Personnel: Trip to South America by Lilian O. Milner, 1958-1959 (Box 18, Folder 10)
      - Executive Committee, 1957-1958 (Box 18, Folder 11)
      - Exhibitions, 1957-1958 (Box 18, Folder 12)
      - Exhibitions: Architecture Display Panels of A.I.A. Centennial for Salisbury, Southern Indonesia, 1957-1959 (Box 18, Folder 13)
      - Exhibitions: Argentine from Museum of Modern Art, Buenos Aires, 1958-1959 (Box 18, Folder 14)
      - Exhibitions: Art from Boston Museum of Art for Japan (Nishinippon Shimbun), 1959-1961 (Box 18, Folder 15)
      - Exhibitions: Artmobile Units for Overseas, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 16)
      - Exhibitions: Biennale de Paris, 1959-1961 (Box 18, Folder 17)
      - Exhibitions: Children's Art from Shankar's Weekly - USIS New Delhi, 1958-1960 (Box 18, Folder 18)
      - Exhibitions: Colombian Art, University of Miami, 1958-1960 (Box 18, Folder 19)
      - Exhibitions: Crafts, Contemporary American from Brussels Fair, 1958-1959 (Box 18, Folder 20)
      - Exhibitions: Exchange of Contemporary American Prints from the Library of Congress to Esslingen, Germany, 1958-1960 (Box 18, Folder 21)
      - Exhibitions: Finnish Art for Beliot, Wisconsin, 1959-1960 (Box 18, Folder 22)
      - Exhibitions: Four Contemporary Paintings from Museum of Modern Art (NYC) in Buenos Aires, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 23)
        Oversized material housed in OV 39
      - Exhibitions: Harrison Cady Works to be Circulated Abroad (Oslo), 1958-1959 (Box 18, Folder 24)
      - Exhibitions: Honoring Independence of Four Latin American Republics, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 25)
      - Exhibitions: Indian Art Sponsored by Asahi Shimbun in Tokyo, Japan, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 26)
      - Exhibitions: Indiana Artists to USSR, 1956-1960 (Box 18, Folder 27)
      - Exhibitions: International Corning Glass Museum, 1958-1959 (Box 18, Folder 28)
      - Exhibitions: International Handicapped, 1960-1961 (Box 18, Folder 29)
      - Exhibitions: Latin American Art at Milwaukee Art Center, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 30)
      - Exhibitions: Minnesota Art Portfolio, circa 1951; 1958-1961 (Box 18, Folder 31)
      - Exhibitions: "One Hundred Years of Architecture in America" for Edinburgh Festival and Tour, 1957-1958 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Fine Arts Committee (FAC) (Box 19)
      - Exhibitions: Paintings from American Collections of German Art, Frankfurt, 1958-1959 (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - Exhibitions: Permanent Painting to Represent U.S. at Birpi, Geneva, 1960-1961 (Box 19, Folder 2)
      - Exhibitions: Polish Artist Sliwinski, 1958-1961 (Box 19, Folder 3)
      - Exhibitions: Rotating Shipboard Art (Moore-McCormack Lines), 1957-1960 (Box 19, Folder 4)
      - Exhibitions: Sister-City Print Show, 1959-1961 (Box 19, Folder 5)
      - Exhibitions: Spanish (of Madrid) by Mexican Painter, A. Pardinas, in the United States, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - Exhibitions: Uruguayan in the United States, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - Foreign Contacts (People), 1958-1960 (Box 19, Folder 8)
      - International Congress of History of Art (Sept. 1961: New York), 1960-1961 (Box 19, Folder 9)
      - International Relations: Individual and Group Projects, 1957-1961 (Box 19, Folder 10)
      - Leaflet (Proposed), circa 1958-1960 (Box 19, Folder 11-12)
      - Materials (General), 1957-1961 (Box 19, Folder 13)
      - Materials: 175th Anniversary of Treaty of Friendship and Commerce Between U.S. and Sweden (1958) (Box 19, Folder 14)
      - Materials: Distribution to First Museum for the Blind, Puerto Rico, 1958-1961 (Box 19, Folder 15)
      - Materials: On Pulaski for Poland, 1959-1961 (Box 19, Folder 16)
      - Materials: On Tadeusz Kosciuszko for Memorial Museum Near Krakow, 1927; 1959-1960 (Box 19, Folder 17-18)
      - Materials: Photos of Fayoum Mummy Portraits in American Collections to Egypt, 1959-1960 (Box 19, Folder 19)
      - Materials: Procurement of, on Abraham Lincoln for Abraham Lincoln Society of India, 1958-1959 (Box 19, Folder 20)
      - Materials: Request for Exchange of Spanish Materials for San Diego Museum of Colonial Artifacts, 1959-1960 (Box 19, Folder 21)
      - Meetings, 1959-1960 (Box 19, Folder 22-23)
      - Members, 1956-1957 (Box 19, Folder 24)
      - News of FAC Members, 1957-1961 (Box 19, Folder 25)
      - Organizing Meeting (Feb. 18, 1957) (Box 19, Folder 26-27)
      - Personnel: Architecture Congress Mexico, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 28)
      - Reports and Meeting Transcript, 1957-1958 (Box 19, Folder 29)
      - Rigault, Jean de, "French Theater on the American Campus", 1954; 1962 (Box 19, Folder 30)
      - Sculpture: Requests for (General), 1958-1960 (Box 19, Folder 31)
      - Sculpture: Requests for Lincoln Bust for Asunción, 1959-1961 (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - Fine Arts Committee (FAC) (Box 20)
      - Sculpture: Request for Lincoln Bust for France 75th Anniversary of Statue of Liberty, 1959-1960 (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - Sculpture: Request for Lincoln Bust for Guayaquil, Ecuador, 1958-1960 (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - Sculpture: Request for Lincoln Bust for San Jose, Costa Rica, 1958-1961 (Box 20, Folder 3)
      - Sculpture: Request for Lincoln Bust for Sydney, Australia, 1958-1961 (Box 20, Folder 4)
      - Sculpture: Request for Lincoln Bust for the University of Bahia, Brazil, 1959 (Box 20, Folder 5)
      - Sculpture: Request for Museum Reproductions for University of San Marcos, Lima, Peru, 1958-1961 (Box 20, Folder 6)
      - Sculpture: Request for Washington Bust for Quito, Ecuador, 1959-1960 (Box 20, Folder 7)
      - Sculpture: Request for Washington Bust for Vera Cruz, Mexico, 1957-1961; 1940s (Box 20, Folder 8)
      - Staff, 1957-1961 (Box 20, Folder 9)
      - Summaries of Activities, 1957-1961 (Box 20, Folder 10-11)
      - Travel by Member of the FAC, Mr. Ridder, to Russia to Photograph Paintings in the Hermitage, Etc., 1958-1959 (Box 20, Folder 12)
      - Visitors to FAC Office, 1957-1961 (Box 20, Folder 13-17)
      - Working Documents, circa 1957-1961 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Foreign Affairs Committee, 1959 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Hobbies Committee, 1957-1960 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Letter Writing Committee, 1958-1961 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Medicine and Health Committee (Project Hope), 1956-1961 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Music Committee, 1957-1961 (Box 20, Folder 23-24)
    - Other Committees, 1957-1961 (Box 20, Folder 25-26)
    - Public Relations Committee, 1957-1959 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Veterans Committee, 1959 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Washington Area Group, 1958-1959 (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Oversized Poster, Exposicion International de Arte Moderno [silkscreen print], circa 1960 (Oversize 39)
      Oversized material from Box 18, Folder 23
- ICA School Files, 1945-1953; Series 5; 7 Linear feet Boxes 21-27
  Found are records of the day and night school including correspondence, class notebooks (attendance books), teacher files recording classes and grades, extensive student files and student enrollment cards, mailing lists, class cards, and notes for classes taught by Robert Richman.
  - Address Cards, A-B, circa 1948-1951 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Applications for Teaching Positions, 1951-1952 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Board of Education, 1949-1952 (Box 21, Folder 3-4)
  - Certificate of Completion, circa 1948-1951 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Class Cards, circa 1948-1951 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    Index cards housed in 2 shoeboxes in Box 27
  - Class Notebooks, 1948-1951 (Box 21, Folder 7-10)
  - Correspondence, 1953; 1951 (Box 21, Folder 11-12)
  - Correspondence, Letters from Schools, 1948-1949 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, Veterans Administration, 1948-1951 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - English 143: Modern Drama [Robert Richman Course?], circa 1948-1951 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Kiln Shed, 1949 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Literature Cards [Robert Richman], circa 1948-1951 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Mailing List, 1948 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Mailing List, General, circa 1948-1951 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous, 1951 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous [Courses and Instructors?], circa 1948-1951 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Notes, Handwritten by Robert Richman, circa 1948-1951 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Schedule for Music Rooms, circa 1948-1951 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - School Recruitment Trip, circa 1948 (Box 21, Folder 24)